shopmania.biz 2011-05-21

# Privacy policy

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for ShopMania BIZ. We are committed to protecting your privacy and encourage you to periodically review this page to be informed of how we protect the information you disclose to us. 

_**Information Collection and Use**_

ShopMania BIZ collects information from our users at several different points on our website. We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature. When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. ShopMania BIZ does not store this information. 

_**Registration**_

In order to utilize this website's full potential, customers need to complete the registration form. During registration, customers are required to give their contact information (such as name and e-mail address). This information is used to inform customers of promotions and new services on our website and will only be used if the customer has shown interest in a particular promotion or service. 

_**Internal Use**_

We may compare and review your personally identifiable information for errors, omissions and accuracy. We may also use your personally identifiable information internally to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, Web Site content and product offerings. Your personally identifiable information may also be used internally to conduct internal research on our users' demographics, interests, behavior and generally to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of our Web Site and our marketing programs. 

_**Order**_

We request information from the user on our order form when making a purchase. Here is where a user must provide their contact information, like name and shipping address, and financial information, like credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill the customer's order. If we have difficulty processing an order, this contact information is used to communicate with the customer. 

_**Cookies**_

To personalize and enhance your browsing and shopping experience, we use a feature on your Internet browser called a cookie. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. We use both session and persistent cookies. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users in the aggregate by analyzing popular areas and products to enhance future experiences on our site. Cookies do not cause damage to your computer systems or files, and only the web site that transferred a particular cookie to you can read, modify or delete such cookie. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there are simple procedures in most browsers that allow you to delete existing cookies, to automatically decline cookies, or to be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer of particular cookies to your computer. Cookies are not used to access information entered on the secure server. This information can be accessed only when you enter your name and password. 

_**Usage Tracking**_

ShopMania BIZ's database tracks the traffic throughout our site. This information is used to compile overall statistics and is not recorded at an individual level. This includes IP (internet protocol) addresses, browser type, ISP (internet service provider), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and #of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate. The statistics help us decide which products and services best serve our members and guests. 

_**Aggregate Information**_

ShopMania BIZ uses aggregate information from demographic surveys, traffic patterns and IP addresses to customize our site. Aggregate information is occasionally shared with third parties for purposes such as planning or executing advertising or promotions. 

_**Sharing**_

ShopMania BIZ gives you access to third party partners to provide you with certain services that are detailed below. ShopMania BIZ will provide that third party with your transaction information and then that third party will collect additional information if needed to provide you with the requested service,such as outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. We reserve the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from users of the site to a third party in the event of any merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of the assets or stock (including without limitation in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings) relating to ShopMania BIZ. Finally, notwithstanding any other provision of this privacy policy to the contrary, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information if we believe that we are required to do so (i) by law; (ii) to comply with legal process or governmental requests; (iii) to enforce our Terms of Service; (iv) to protect our operations or those of any affiliated entities; (v) to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of ShopMania BIZ, any affiliated entities, you or others; and (vi) to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain. 

_**Third Party Links**_

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by ShopMania BIZ. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work). 

_**Newsletters**_

If you request an email newsletter subscription, we will send you an email confirming your request. This confirmation process allows you to unsubscribe if you changed your mind and decided not to join the list. Furthermore, the confirmation email will alert you if someone else had entered your email address into our email newsletter. In order to make our emails more relevant and useful to you, our servers may receive a confirmation when you open email from ShopMania BIZ. On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send you an e-mail. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though you can deactivate your account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

_**Unsolicited E-mail (SPAM)**_

Your privacy is very important to us. Be assured that, in accordance with this privacy policy, we do not sell or distribute our customer list to third parties. You should be aware, however, that unscrupulous marketers can sometimes "harvest" your e-mail address directly from your computer or another person's address book or even obtain your e-mail address through programs that automatically search web pages and e-mail traffic for e-mail addresses. 

_**Surveys and Sweepstakes**_

From time to time, our site requests information from users via surveys or sweepstakes. Participation in these surveys or sweepstakes is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name, shipping address and e-mail address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

_**Security**_

ShopMania BIZ takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the Secure Socket Layers (SSLs) encryption software. While on a secure page, such as our order form, a lock icon appears on the bottom of your Web browser. When you are not on a secure page, no lock icon will appear. In addition, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment under restricted access. 

_**Special Offers**_

Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special offers and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below. 

_**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating**_

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code, phone, e-mail or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate that user's personally identifiable information provided to us. This can be done by using the unsubscribe feature in our communication. 

_**Refer a Friend**_

Using a ShopMania BIZ form, you can also refer a friend to the ShopMania BIZ Web Site. You and your friend's names and e-mail addresses are requested to ensure that your friend will know that you have requested that ShopMania BIZ send them an e-mail. You and your friend's e-mail addresses will only be used for this purpose unless permission is otherwise granted. 

_**Choice/Opt-Out**_

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. Users who no longer wish to receive promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by using the unsubscribe feature in our e-mail. 

_**Children Under Age**_

ShopMania BIZ is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under age without verifiable parental consent. If you are under age, please do not provide personally identifiable information of any kind whatsoever. 

_**Service Providers**_

We may share your personally identifiable information with authorized third party partners, agents and contractors. For example, if we need to ship something to you, we must share your name and address with a shipping company. Examples of other third parties that we may share your personal information with include: webhosting companies, fulfillment companies (e.g., companies that fulfill product orders), jewelers, assemblers, data analysis firms, affiliates, third party consulting or marketing firms and e-mail service providers. Additionally, if you use a credit card or other financing alternative to place an order with ShopMania BIZ, to confirm and process your order we will share your personally identifiable information with such financing company. These third parties only receive personally identifiable information if such information is needed to perform their function(s), and they are not authorized to use any personally identifiable information for any other purpose(s) other than the purpose(s) set forth by ShopMania BIZ. We only provide third-parties with the minimum amount of personally identifiable information necessary to complete the requested service, product or transaction 

_**Compliance with Law and Fraud Protection**_

We may collect and disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. We may collect and possibly share personally identifiable information and any other information available to us in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any personal or as otherwise required by law. We may also exchange information, including personally identifiable information, with other companies and organizations for credit fraud protection and risk reduction. 

_**Questions and Feedback**_

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue. 

_**Changes to This Policy**_

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy, and any of our policies or procedures concerning the treatment of information collected through the site, without prior notice. You can determine when this privacy policy was last revised by referring to date at the top of this page. Any changes to our privacy policy will become effective upon posting of the revised policy on the Internet, accessible through the site. Use of the site following such changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised policy then in effect. We encourage you to periodically review our privacy policy to ensure familiarity with our most current version. 

_**Your Consent**_

By using our Web site (including through our customer service line), you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of information in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy. We reserve the right to modify or amend this policy at any time. If we ever change our privacy policy, we will post any changes on this page or send you an e-mail so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Unless we clearly state otherwise, the changes to our privacy policy will affect only the information we collect after the effective date of the change. 

_**How to Contact Us**_

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [biz@shopmania.com](mailto:biz@shopmania.com).
